

 $\overline{\phantom{a}}$ 

marko\_vu@hotmail.com

0607052855

9

Belgrade, Serbia

in

linkedin.com/in/markovujosevic

 $\bigcirc$ 

github.com/markovu91

# **SKILLS**

Java

Spring Core

Hibernate

MySQL

Servlets&JSP

Git

HTML5

CSS3

Spring Boot

JavaScript

# **LANGUAGES**

#### Serbian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

#### Germar

Elementary Proficiency

# **INTERESTS**

Web Design

Software Development

Engineering

Aviation

Music Production

# Marko Vujosevic

Java Developer

Highly motivated graduate. Looking forward to get more experience in software development and work as a part of a team. Communicative, ambitious, responsible and adaptive to new surroundings, with a strong desire for learning new technologies.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Java Development**

IT Academy

11/2017 - 01/2019

Belgrade

Belgrade

# **Road and Urban Traffic Engineering**Faculty of Traffic and Transportation Engineering

09/2010 - 09/2015

## PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Simple Chat Application

- Chat application with Sockets and Java IO
- https://github.com/markovu91/ChatGuiApplication

#### JavaScript Calculator

- Javascript Web calculator with css flexbox
- markovu91/Calculator: Simple calculator using javascript with flexbox (github.com)

### User Management Web Application

- User Management Web Application using Servlet, JSP, JDBC, MySQL.
- markovu91/Servlet-JSP-JDBC-Crud: User Management Web Application (github.com)

#### **Employee Management System**

- Simple desktop employee management system application with basic interaction with database, using Swing as a gui and JDBC.
- https://github.com/markovu91/EmployeeApp

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Java Developer Intern Softmetrix

10/2019 - 11/2019 Achievements/Tasks Belgrade

- Collaborated with team members to design gradebook MVC web application for School.
- Used technologies (Spring Boot, Git, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, MySQL).

#### **Advisor Trainee**

# Serbian Association Of International Road Hauliers

10/2016 - 05/2017 Belgrade

#### CERTIFICATES

Sertificate of completion intership programme at Softmetrix (Java Development) (10/2019 - 11/2019)

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Third place award at the student competition of France-Serbian Chamber of Commerce for the title "How we will move into the future?" (2014)

Written essay about the future of transportation and alternative energy technologies